Guide to the Alan Sondheim Papers MSS.267
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I. Written Work
  - "Two Modes," Meta Ltd., Undated (Box 52, Folder 23)
  - "Two Poems Beginning With Lines From Dante", Undated (Box 52, Folder 24)
  - "Two Short Poems", Undated (Box 52, Folder 25)
  - "Typed Glossolalia: Computer Analysis of Determinism in Man", 1972 (Box 52, Folder 26)
  - "Uncertain Theory", Undated (Box 52, Folder 27)
  - Untitled Works, Undated (Box 52, Folder 28, 29, 30, Box 53, Folder 1, 2, 3, 4, Box 54, Folder 1, 2, 3)
  - "Untitled Statement for Catalog", Undated (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - "Upon Completing Gorky's 'Life of Matvei Kozhemyakin' ", Undated (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - "UT", Undated (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - "V", Undated (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - "VA", Undated (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - "Vaginality", 1982 (Box 54, Folder 9, 10)
  - "Vaginality: Appendix", Undated (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - "Vaginality: Appendix in Relation to Catastrophe Theory", Undated (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - "(Vaginality) Diachronic: Histories and Originations", Undated (Box 54, Folder 13)
  - "Vaginality: Mathemation", Undated (Box 54, Folder 14)
  - "Vaginality: Remnants of a Physiological Essay", 1982 (Box 54, Folder 15)
  - "Verge", Undated (Box 54, Folder 16)
  - "Vignette", Undated (Box 54, Folder 17)
  - "Virga", Undated (Box 54, Folder 18)
  - "Various Titles", Undated (Box 54, Folder 19)
  - "Various Titles (Structures of Reality)," Meta Ltd, Undated (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - "Vascular Trilithon", Undated (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - "Video Texts," Perforations 2, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - "Village", 1969-1970 (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - "Violation Fabric", 1974 (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - "Visual Art", Undated (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - "W", 1978 (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - "The Wake… The Watch", Undated (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - "Walkingz", Undated (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - "Wall", Undated (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - "Walls Rug [Somewhere]", 1970 (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - "War Fever", 1963 (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - "Water", 1973 (Box 55, Folder 13)
  - "Water", 1988 (Box 55, Folder 14)
  - "Waver", Undated (Box 55, Folder 15)
  - "The Way It Works in My Family", Undated (Box 55, Folder 16)
  - The Wayward, 2004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_17)
  - "Wds. Inscribed Upon a Drawing of a Hand", Undated (Box 55, Folder 17)
  - "We All Make Mistakes: L'Eclisse", Undated (Box 55, Folder 18)
  - "The Weeds", Undated (Box 55, Folder 19)
  - "We Wager Their Resoluteness Surely Overcomes", Undated (Box 55, Folder 20)
  - "What Can I Say?", Undated (Box 55, Folder 21)
  - "What I Believe", Undated (Box 55, Folder 22)
  - "What I Do", Undated (Box 55, Folder 23)
  - "What If", Undated (Box 55, Folder 24)
  - "What I Wish To Write", Undated (Box 55, Folder 25)
  - "What the Engine Does, of the Anorectic Airliner", Undated (Box 55, Folder 26)
  - "When I Found Out About the Children", Undated (Box 55, Folder 27)
  - "When the Chief of the Secret Police Becomes the Leader of the Country", Undated (Box 55, Folder 28)
  - "When the Elders Lose Their True Position", Undated (Box 55, Folder 29)
  - "When We Are Getting Along in This This Time of Our Lives (Filmscript)", Undated (Box 55, Folder 30)
  - "Whistler's Children", 1971 (Box 55, Folder 31)
  - William Louis Sørensen, August 1971 (Box 55, Folder 32)
  - "The Wind Coming From the Dark Cabinet", Undated (Box 55, Folder 33)
  - "Window", Undated (Box 55, Folder 34)
  - "Within and Without the Thinking of George Stone", 1988 (Box 55, Folder 35)
  - "The Woman (Who) Leaves", Undated (Box 55, Folder 36)
  - "The Work of Robert Horvitz in Relation to Inscription Typology", Undated (Box 55, Folder 37)
  - "The Workingman's Ballad of the Return to Decency at the End", Undated (Box 55, Folder 38)
  - "(Working Outline, Sick and Violent Love)", Undated (Box 55, Folder 39)
  - "Working Down from the Universal Set - The Photograph", Undated (Box 55, Folder 40)
  - "Working Up from the Null Set", Undated (Box 55, Folder 41)
  - "Writing", Undated (Box 55, Folder 42)
  - "Writing for the Return of It," Art Papers, 1991 (Box 55, Folder 43)
  - "Writings," Tasmanian School of Art, 1982 (Box 55, Folder 44)
  - " 'You Do Seem To Deconstruct Power Whenever You Have the Chance, Alan' ", Undated (Box 55, Folder 45)
  - "ZBS", 1976 (Box 55, Folder 46)
  - ZZ, 2004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_18)
- Series II. Visual Art
  Series II. Visual Art includes Sondheim's photography as well as drawn, painted, printed, and digitally created work on paper, canvas, and digital files. This series also includes some work by Sondheim's contemporaries and collaborators, such as Mike Metz, Margaret Curtis, Stelarc, and Beth Cannon. Much of Sondeim's work includes sexual content and nudity, and viewer discretion is advised. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - "1 2 3" To-do list with attached photographs, Undated (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - "4-3-2-0" Hypercube Projection Images, Undated (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - 4 x 4 Generated Symmetries, Undated (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - "aA" Art Print by Jim Andrews, Undated (Box 77, Folder 20)
  - "A.S. in G.A." Photojournal, Undated (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Aerial Photographs, circa 1960-1990 (Box 62, Box 63)
  - Aerial Photographs, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Alan Sondheim and David Finkelstein Photographs, Undated (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Alan Sondheim portrait by V. Elizabeth Turk, 1987 (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Alan Sondheim Portraits, Undated (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Art Print from R. Mal (?), 1974 (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - Artwork by T. Z. for Alan Sondheim, 1983-1986 (Box 78, Folder 7)
  - "Azure Bird" Photo Series, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_35)
  - "Azure Costume" Photo Series, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_36)
  - "Babble Studies", 1993 (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - "Babble Studies (Banners)", 1992 (Box 78, Folder 13)
  - "Babble Studies: Knots", 1993 (Box 78, Folder 14)
  - Balloon Dance Photo Series, 2003 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_61)
  - "Bandage / Bones" Digital Art Series, 2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_37)
  - Beth Cannon Artwork, 1973 (Box 58, Folder 8, Box 78, Folder 15)
  - "Bobig" Canvas Piece, 2005 (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - "Bush League / Bush Whacked" Photo Series, 2005 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - "Chart of Activity of Measuring Body Resistance", Undated (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Cityscape Photographs, circa 1960-1990 (Box 62, Box 63, Box 65, Box 66)
  - "Dance Sphere" Photo/Video Series, 2005-2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_38)
  - Descriptions of Photography Series, Undated (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Digital Art - 3D Modeling and Avatars, 2004-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_62)
  - Digital Art - 3D Scanning, 1999-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_63)
    These images and videos were created with early 3D-Scanning technology including the VIVID-700, Cyrax Laser Scanner, Polhemus motion tracking, and Geomagic Studio.
  - Digital Art - Blender, 2006-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_64)
  - Digital Art - Calculon, 2004-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_65)
  - Digital Art - Image Archive, 1994-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_66)
  - Digital Art - Plotted Images, 1994-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_67)
    3D and 2D graphic images with coordinates, textures, and other properties defined by text files (common formats are .OBJ and .MTL). Both images and their companion files are found here.
  - "Disorders of the Real" Photo / Text Collage, circa 1990 (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Dot Matrix Portraits, Undated (Box 77, Folder 17)
  - "Dreamland" Photo Series, 2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_39)
  - Dunlap Tires - Photo Slides, 1988 (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - "Early Musical Phenakistiscope", Undated (Box 77, Folder 19)
  - "E Hate / An Interruption / A Mob", 1984 (Box 58, Folder 14)
  - Electron Microscope Photos, circa 1965-1980 (Box 58, Folder 15, Box 59, Folder 11, 12, 13, Box 61, Folder Unknown, Folder 4)
  - Emily Cheng Art Print, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 1989)
  - "Equation" Digital Art Series, 2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_40)
  - Experimental Photographs, 1970-2008 (Box 58, Folder 16, 17, Box 76)
  - "Eye" Photo Series, 2008-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_41)
  - Figure Drawings, Undated (Box 27, Folder 2, 3)
  - Figure Drawings (Damaged Life), Undated (Box 58, Folder 18)
  - "Firefly and Rail" Photo Series, 2008-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_42)
  - "Florida" Photo Series, 2001 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_43)
  - "Garden" Photo/Video Series, 2006-2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_44)
  - Geometric Drawings, 1969-1974 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - "The Generation of Triangles" Drawing, Undated (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - "Glade" Photo/Video Series, 2001-2003 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_45)
  - "Glass" Photo Series, 2004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_46)
  - "Gorge" Photo/Video Series, 2004-2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_47)
  - "Grl" Photo Series, 2005 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_48)
  - Halifax Flying Club Photographs, Undated (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - "He His Eyes Closed", Undated (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - "Hills for Dancing" and "Other Dancers", 1970 (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Hogu Art Print, 1989 (Box 78, Folder 5)
  - "Hollywood (Hollywood)" Photodocumentary Book, 1983 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Internet Text Images (Computer print outs), 1999 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - "Internet Work" Photo Slides, 1995 (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - "It's My Bag", Undated (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Jennifer, Julu, and Nikuko, 1997-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_68)
  - Kara Walker, Crown Camera Photo Slides, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Laura Parker Photographs, 1979-1981 (Box 77, Folder 18)
  - "Lights" Photo Series, 2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_49)
  - "Lore" Photo/Video Series, 2005 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_50)
  - "Lur" Photo/Sound Series, 2006-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_51)
  - Mathematical Artwork, Undated (Box 78, Folder 8)
  - "Maximax" Photo/Text Series, 2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_52)
  - "Miami" Photo/Text Series, 2001-2004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_53)
  - Motion Tracking - Photos and Digital Art, 2006-2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_69)
    These files include both digital art created with motion tracking technology, as well as photographs in the studio as the art was being created. Technology used includes Polhemus.
  - "Multi" Photo Series, 2008-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_54)
  - Nature Photography, circa 1960-1990 (Box 62)
  - "Neuropteris" Digital Art/Text Series, 2006-2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_55)
  - "Origins of Measure" Digital Art Series, 2006-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_56)
  - Photo series related to unspecified videotapes, 1969-1979 (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Photo slides of mathematical texts, 1973 (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Photographs taken in Aurora, Colorado, 2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_70)
  - Photography - Historical Sources and Religious Texts, 2006-2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_71)
  - Photography - Japanese and Chinese Art and Calligraphy, 2004-2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_72)
  - Photography - Musical Instruments, 2002-2010 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_73)
  - Photography - Nature, 1994-2010 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_74)
  - Photography - Nude, 1996-2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_75)
  - Photography - Portraits and Candids, 1996-2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_76)
  - Photography - Studios and Workspaces, 2000-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_77)
  - Photography - Travel and Cityscapes, 1994-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_78)
  - Photos from an untitled album, Undated (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Plotted Graphic Images, Undated (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Polaroid work, including stills from videotapes, Undated (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - "Pomurder" Photo/Video Series, 2006 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_57)
  - Postcards, Undated (Box 60, Folder 6, 7)
  - Ppress Magazine - Broadsides, circa 1960-1980 (Box 60, Folder 8, 9, Box 61, Folder 1, 2)
  - Rhode Island School of Design - Newspaper Press Cards, Undated (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - "Rod Songs (Look, Act, Dream), 1991 (Box 78, Folder 16)
  - "Rod Songs: U.S. Customs", 1992 (Box 78, Folder 17)
  - "Rosa's Argument", 1978-1999 (Box 77, Folder 21)
  - "Scribe" Photo Series, 2004 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_58)
  - "Shamans of the Blind Country" Photographs by Michael Oppitz, 1978-1979 (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - "Sheet of Assertions," Geometric Drawings, Undated (Box 78, Folder 24)
  - "Short Story", 1970 (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Shūji (Japanese Calligraphy), Undated (Box 78, Folder 6)
  - "Stereotypes", 1994 (Box 78, Folder 18)
  - "Stereotypes: Object Lessons", 1993 (Box 78, Folder 19)
  - Stills for Inserts: "Tasmania… the Film", 1983 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - "Symmetries" Graphical Drawings, Undated (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - "Tanka" Photo Series, 2007 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_59)
  - "Tasmania" Photographs, Undated (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Travel Potography, circa 1960-1990 (Box 62, Box 63, Box 64, Box 65, Box 66, Box 76)
  - "Trilby" Photo Series, 2002-2005 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_60)
  - "Untitled", 1987 (Box 78, Folder 21)
  - Untitled photo album, Undated (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Untitled pieces, Undated (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Untitled Printed Piece, Undated (Box 77, Folder 22)
  - "Williamstown and Fort Miller, NY", 1976 (Box 78, Folder 22)
  - Works by other artists, 1971-1991 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  - Xerox Photo Collage, Undated (Box 78, Folder 23)
- Series III. Musical Recordings
  Series III. Musical Recordings includes Sondheim's musical work, as a solo artist and as a member of Damaged Life and Ritual-All-7-70 (often referred to as "All"), on audio reels, audiocassettes, and digital files. The record titles are taken from either the tape's written label or the digital file's name. This series also includes written documents pertaining to Sondheim's musical career, such as set lists, performance flyers, liner notes, and circuitry diagrams. This series is arranged alphabetically.
  - 121 Back - S-Original, Undated (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_089)
  - 20,000 / 1 / 20,000, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_230, Box 13, Audiocassette 267_187)
  - 3rd Heather Session, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_244)
  - "349"; "Live Mix" (on WREK radio); Jarboe; Chris Schwartz; Arthur Davis, Undated (Box 15, Audiocassette 267_465)
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    The audiocassette sits in a large hand-painted case portraying a red and black silhouette on a deep purple background.
  - 52, Undated; cuid30311 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_130)
  - A General Description of the World, Alan Sondheim, Undated; cuid30312 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_129)
  - "Aafghan" Digital Audio Series, 2006-2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_80)
  - Adrian Pipui and Alan Sondheim, Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_343)
  - Alan Sondheim, March 19, 1974 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_365)
  - Alan Sondheim, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_201)
    Note says "Jona Lewie, Ry Cooder, Bop Til You Drop"
  - Alan Sondheim - 2nd Duplicate, 1971-1975 (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_172)
    Note says "plus background references." Roll 3 is dated February 7, 1975 and Roll 4 is dated February 10, 1975.
  - Alan Sondheim Interview - L. Thornton, L. Peckham, D. de la Cerde, T. Zummer, February 22, 1987 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_360)
  - Alan's Tape, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_300)
  - All 770, October 29, 1967; cuid30309 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_132)
  - Alvin Lucier - Music on a Long Thin Wire, circa 1992 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_355)
  - "Ama / Amab" Digital Audio Series, 2008 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_81)
  - Andes, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_225)
  - Andy / Alan on Thater [Illegible], Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_358)
  - Andy James, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_228)
  - Angeline Soundtrack, Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_336)
  - Antigone Tape, 1967 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_099)
  - The Antithesis to Recessive Ideologies 12345 (music) 54321, February 4, 1978; cuid30303 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_124)
    Audio reel 267_124 identified as moldy on December 6, 2021. Theis item is currently isolated from other items by housing it in a polyethylene bag with a desiccated board and RH monitor strip. If this strip indicates an RH greater than 50%, the Preservation department should be contacted ASAP. Do not open this packaging without contacting the Preservation Department.
  - Arrangement #1 - Electronic, Undated (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_055)
  - Ascending Pulse Echo / Descending, Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_361)
  - "Avatar ESP" - Audio Recordings and Liner Notes, 2003-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_82)
  - Background Music, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_260)
    Other labels on the tape say, "Home Movie Soundtrack" and "Mix for Millennium."
  - Background Music 2: 123 Damaged Life / Despair Soundtrack, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_163)
  - Background Music with Voice, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_158)
  - Background / Tango, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_175)
  - Bantok Rock, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_151)
  - Bass Recorder Breath Piano, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_188)
  - Because I'm a Woman Jarboe, 1984 (Box 15, Audiocassette 267_464, Box 67, Folder 15)
    Audiocassette was rehoused; original container and artwork kept in Box 67.
  - Being With Him - Clara, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_277)
  - BeMe Seed, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_305, Box 15, Audiocassette 267_463, Box 67, Folder 16)
    Handwritten liner notes included.
  - Biblical Piece Using Language and Gesenus Dictionary [first line of Genesis]: Spoken, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_177)
  - Big Stick Crack'n'Drag and Lizzy Mercer Descloux / Factrix, Cazzaza, California Bablyon, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_309)
  - Blues, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_199)
  - Bob Leigh Interview, Undated; cuid30292 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_113)
  - Bohm, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_150)
    Note says "foghorn."
  - "Boojum" Digital Audio Series with Liner Notes, 2007-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_83)
  - Boredoms - "Pop Tatari", Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_169)
  - Bottle Hill, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_218)
  - Brasil I, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_196)
  - Breath Piece, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_205)
  - Brox / Bicks, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_160)
    Note says "Moscow ETC"
  - Buffalo City Council Sample, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_223)
  - Buffalo Gals, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_219)
  - C#-D Melodica, Guitar Filled Intervals, Lips Echo, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_231)
  - Cadere in Memorium with Andy Karp / Arithmetic of Signifiers, 1983-1984 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_368)
    Microcassette
  - Cadererlin / Memories [Illegible], Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_284)
  - Carey Driving Young Durk [Illegible], Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_293)
  - Casio, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_226)
  - Cauldron by Alan Sondheim, Helena Espvall and Azure Carter, 2011 (Box 22, Sound disc--vinyl 267_788)
    This LP features Alan Sondheim on acoustic-electric guitar, guzheng, oud, alpine zither, and ukulele; Azure Carter's voice; and Helena Espvall on cello. It was produced by Fire Museum Records in association with Tequila Sunrise Records.
  - Chant, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_250)
  - Christen Hennui and Alan Sondheim on Topores, NYC at the Waters, August 31, 1975 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_352)
    The cassette's handwritten label is difficult to read.
  - Christians in a Dead World, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_299)
  - "Cithara" Digital Audio Series, 2006-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_84)
  - Citizen Hostage Big Talk #1, 1984 (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_239)
  - Clark Coolidge Conversation with Alan Sondheim, Fall, 1966; cuid30301 (Box 24, Quarter inch audio reel 267_123)
  - "Cobza" Digital Audio Series, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_85)
  - Compactor Tapes, Undated (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_088)
  - Computer Operation, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_186)
  - Concert at St. Mark's - Reading, Electronics, Guitar, November 10, 1975 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_327, 267_363, Box 13, Audiocassette 267_176)
  - Concert with Laurie Audura / Notes on Nancy [Illegible], Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_339)
  - Continuation, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_274)
  - Conversation with G. H. [Illegible], Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_367)
  - "Cord" Digital Audio Series, 2000-2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_86)
  - Craw - 3 Songs, Undated (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_314)
  - Cricket, Undated (Box 12, Audiocassette 267_224)
  - "Cura Saz" Digital Audio Series, 2009 (Box Electronic Records, E-records FA_MSS_267_ER_87)
  - Dairy Queen Empire, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_168)
  - ESP-DISK Recording Contract, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Damaged Life - 123 Nicaragua Sex Master, November 30, 1986 (Box 22, Quarter inch audio reel 267_068)
  - Damaged Life - Album and Performance Notes, circa 1986-1988 (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Damaged Life Compilation, August 9, 1986 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_072, Box 14, Audiocassette 267_356)
    This tape also includes a duplicate master of "Global Report" by Damaged Life. The tape is reverse wound.
  - Damaged Life / Devo, Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_331)
  - Damaged Life - Film Music, Undated (Box 13, Audiocassette 267_159)
  - Damaged Life - Flesh, 1987 (Box 25, Quarter inch audio reel 267_102)
  - Damaged Life - Flesh at 123 Club, Undated (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_347)
  - Damaged Life - Flyers for Performances and Albums, circa 1986-1988 (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Damaged Life - Global Report, 1986 (Box 22, Quarter inch audio reel 267_067, Box 14, Audiocassette 267_349, 267_350, Box 11, Audiocassette 267_317, Box 13, Audiocassette 267_161, Box 67, Folder 14)
    Artwork and liner notes included.
  - Damaged Life - Lips, 1987 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_289, 267_316, 267_320)
  - Damaged Life - Live at Intermedia, May 13, 1988 (Box 14, Audiocassette 267_342)
  - Damaged Life - Live at the Starck Club, July 31, 1987 (Box 1, Vhs 267_567, Box 2, U-matic 267_574, Box 3, U-matic 267_596, Box 14, Audiocassette 267_337, 267_340, 267_341)
    According to the tape labels, each tape shows a recording from a different camera. 267_567 and 267_341 are the video and audio from Fran's camera. 267_574 is the "2nd camera, Fran and Rich Gold, silent, to be synced up with Marlis Schmidt's camera (Master)." 267_596 is Marlis Schmidt's camera - it's label also says "2nd tape with sound. Alan Sondheim, Denise de la Cerda, Devonna Walker, Randal Davis, Dallas. Master."
  - Damaged Life - "Machine", February 17, 1986 (Box 11, Audiocassette 267_288)
  - Damaged Life - "Repressive Circuitry", August, 1986 (Box 23, Quarter inch audio reel 267_093)